FIND ME





# **Padelis Theodosiou**

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

## **ABOUT ME**

Passionated about building excellent software that improves the lives of those around me. Specialized in creating software for clients rangings from individuals and small businesses all the way to large enterprise corporations.

P: +30 6974155996 W: padelis.theodosiou.me

E: padelis.theodosiou@gmail.com

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Software Developer Internship

The Smalls

mar. 2018 - aug. 2018

Developed a number of Windows-based applications using C#, .NET and a couple of web applications using HTML/(S)CSS and JavaScript. Also, I was responsible for the maintenance and development of WordPress themes and plugins.

#### **Software Developer**

Blockachain

sep. 2019 - dec. 2019

Involved in the development process of various web applications for European projects. Used innovating technologies and Agile software development methodology.

#### Software Developer

Athens Technology dec. 2019 - present Center

Involved in the development process of various web applications for European projects. Using innovating technologies and Agile software development methodology.

#### **EDUCATION**

Diploma in Automotive Engineering 2010 - 2013

#### 1st Vocational Senior High Scool

Learned how to design and build the mechanical systems of cars. Received theoretical knowledge as well as laboratory work in electrical and mechanical engineering.

B.Sc in Computer Science and Engineering sep. 2014 - jul. 2019

# University of Thessaly (prev. TEI of Thessaly)

Learned how to articulate ideas, fell in love with learning, participated in meetups for various topics ( web dev, operating systems ), developed a number of applications and discovered a passion for the arts.